所以我们应该先系统地清点一遍里面的...
so we should systematically take a full inventory of ev--
我的天  那是手持催眠枪吗
Oh, my god. Is that a handheld hypno-beam?
原版试用品之一
One of the original betas.
看到底部这个按钮了吗
See how it has the switch on the bottom?
成品把它挪到侧面了
The production models moved it to the side.
这太棒了
This is amazing.
都可以媲美
Almost as cool as a...
-晶体管冲击波枪  -晶体管冲击波枪
- Transistorized blast gun. - Transistorized blast gun.
好吧
Ah, ha ha. Okay.
你们俩可以过后再缠绵
The two of you can get a room later,
我们现在要赶飞机了
but we have a plane to catch.
别动
No.
他们在哪买的这东西  漫画书背面吗
Where did they buy this stuff, from the back of a comic book?
不  姑娘  那不是蜂鸣器  那是
No, girl, that's not really a joy buzzer. That's a --
电磁脉冲
E.M.P.